{
  "subject": "mathematics",
  "grade": "first_grade",
  "question_count": 150,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1979",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 + 2?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2088",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 - 9?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7020",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 + 17?",
      "answer": "34",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 34
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4340",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 + 9?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4712",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 19?",
      "answer": "0",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 19,
        "result": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3046",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 + 20?",
      "answer": "40",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 40
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7814",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 + 9?",
      "answer": "20",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 20
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1712",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 + 12?",
      "answer": "32",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 32
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_9987",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 8?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6121",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 + 9?",
      "answer": "26",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 26
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8657",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 - 6?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8242",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 1?",
      "answer": "14",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4181",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 + 1?",
      "answer": "19",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2355",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 + 2?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3325",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 - 2?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3780",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 8?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8992",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 5?",
      "answer": "14",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_9479",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 + 9?",
      "answer": "20",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 20
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1685",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 + 12?",
      "answer": "32",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 32
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7391",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 + 6?",
      "answer": "26",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 26
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2987",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 2 + 11?",
      "answer": "13",
      "variables": {
        "a": 2,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6495",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 2?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8293",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 + 6?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7817",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 + 9?",
      "answer": "29",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 29
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7523",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 - 8?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1372",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 9?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8890",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 - 7?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3180",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 1?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6030",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 5?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1600",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 + 17?",
      "answer": "34",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 34
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8320",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 4?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1571",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 - 1?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8617",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 3 + 8?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 3,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2515",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 13 + 18?",
      "answer": "31",
      "variables": {
        "a": 13,
        "b": 18,
        "result": 31
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7340",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 4?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2374",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 + 3?",
      "answer": "23",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2744",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 + 17?",
      "answer": "33",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 33
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_5191",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 18?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 18,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7360",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 5?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2497",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 - 4?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_5227",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 + 14?",
      "answer": "22",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 14,
        "result": 22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8438",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 20?",
      "answer": "0",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6251",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 1?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_5697",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 - 2?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3626",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 3?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_9140",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 5 + 12?",
      "answer": "17",
      "variables": {
        "a": 5,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 17
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3825",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 15?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8350",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 + 7?",
      "answer": "13",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_9628",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 + 7?",
      "answer": "24",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 24
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7454",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 + 3?",
      "answer": "13",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7003",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 - 2?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3265",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 + 13?",
      "answer": "29",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 13,
        "result": 29
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_5697",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 14?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 14,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6698",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 + 2?",
      "answer": "22",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_9719",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 7?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4250",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 + 11?",
      "answer": "19",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 19
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3247",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 11?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3806",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 + 15?",
      "answer": "24",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 24
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7356",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 7?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6942",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 8?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3101",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 + 20?",
      "answer": "30",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 30
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3807",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 15?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8565",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 + 12?",
      "answer": "26",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 26
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1048",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 14?",
      "answer": "21",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 14,
        "result": 21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4796",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 + 10?",
      "answer": "24",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 24
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3944",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 15?",
      "answer": "0",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3018",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 + 20?",
      "answer": "31",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 31
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6596",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 12?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2417",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 5 - 3?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 5,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7277",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 - 11?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3935",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 8?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3571",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 20?",
      "answer": "27",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 27
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4980",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 14?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 14,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2824",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 1?",
      "answer": "13",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6804",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 + 12?",
      "answer": "21",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4068",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 5?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7352",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 12?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2648",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 + 8?",
      "answer": "28",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8299",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 16?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3623",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 12?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_9680",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 11?",
      "answer": "6",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 6
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6451",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 + 14?",
      "answer": "23",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 14,
        "result": 23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8820",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 10?",
      "answer": "22",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1704",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 + 8?",
      "answer": "28",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_5468",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 13 - 3?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 13,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8439",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 12?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7905",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 15?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8705",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 9?",
      "answer": "7",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 7
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6509",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 3?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_5770",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 + 15?",
      "answer": "24",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 24
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1987",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 1 + 13?",
      "answer": "14",
      "variables": {
        "a": 1,
        "b": 13,
        "result": 14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8710",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 6?",
      "answer": "14",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_5803",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 2?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8531",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 + 6?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4432",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 - 9?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7235",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 + 8?",
      "answer": "17",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 17
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6791",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 17?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4483",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 - 7?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4129",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 - 12?",
      "answer": "0",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8564",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 8?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_5408",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 + 4?",
      "answer": "14",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 14
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8395",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 8?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3904",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 2 + 19?",
      "answer": "21",
      "variables": {
        "a": 2,
        "b": 19,
        "result": 21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1556",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 3?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4045",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 + 17?",
      "answer": "23",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2947",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 6?",
      "answer": "13",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 13
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1506",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 5?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3141",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 + 11?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8977",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 + 3?",
      "answer": "23",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 23
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3505",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 - 4?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3400",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 9?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4352",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 13 + 17?",
      "answer": "30",
      "variables": {
        "a": 13,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 30
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2551",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 - 1?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 1,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1099",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 - 12?",
      "answer": "0",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 0
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_9829",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 - 5?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2047",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 + 12?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6260",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 16 - 15?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 16,
        "b": 15,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_5630",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 + 12?",
      "answer": "27",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 27
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_9865",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 1 + 3?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 1,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3316",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 3 + 9?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 3,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6882",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 + 20?",
      "answer": "39",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 39
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2213",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 + 7?",
      "answer": "22",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 7,
        "result": 22
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2771",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 11?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6905",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 13 + 3?",
      "answer": "16",
      "variables": {
        "a": 13,
        "b": 3,
        "result": 16
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_5960",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 19?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 19,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2941",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 1 + 20?",
      "answer": "21",
      "variables": {
        "a": 1,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4562",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 5?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1062",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 15 + 13?",
      "answer": "28",
      "variables": {
        "a": 15,
        "b": 13,
        "result": 28
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8867",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 - 2?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 2,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2517",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 11?",
      "answer": "18",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 18
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8651",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 17?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 17,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4796",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 16?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6030",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 12 - 10?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 12,
        "b": 10,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7986",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 - 5?",
      "answer": "5",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 5
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2660",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 8?",
      "answer": "12",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 12
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4108",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 11 + 4?",
      "answer": "15",
      "variables": {
        "a": 11,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 15
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1443",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 9 - 5?",
      "answer": "4",
      "variables": {
        "a": 9,
        "b": 5,
        "result": 4
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2707",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 7 + 14?",
      "answer": "21",
      "variables": {
        "a": 7,
        "b": 14,
        "result": 21
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6769",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 19 - 8?",
      "answer": "11",
      "variables": {
        "a": 19,
        "b": 8,
        "result": 11
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_5200",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 17 - 16?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 17,
        "b": 16,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_6628",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 8 - 6?",
      "answer": "2",
      "variables": {
        "a": 8,
        "b": 6,
        "result": 2
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3841",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 13 + 20?",
      "answer": "33",
      "variables": {
        "a": 13,
        "b": 20,
        "result": 33
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_2106",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 12?",
      "answer": "8",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 12,
        "result": 8
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1508",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 20 - 19?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 20,
        "b": 19,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_3001",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 11?",
      "answer": "3",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 11,
        "result": 3
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_5024",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 14 - 13?",
      "answer": "1",
      "variables": {
        "a": 14,
        "b": 13,
        "result": 1
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_1855",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 6 + 4?",
      "answer": "10",
      "variables": {
        "a": 6,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 10
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_4248",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 10 + 19?",
      "answer": "29",
      "variables": {
        "a": 10,
        "b": 19,
        "result": 29
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_7288",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 2,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 18 - 9?",
      "answer": "9",
      "variables": {
        "a": 18,
        "b": 9,
        "result": 9
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "mathematics_1_8188",
      "subject": "mathematics",
      "grade": "first_grade",
      "topic": "arithmetic",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "type": "generated",
      "question": "What is 4 - 4?",
      "answer": "0",
      "variables": {
        "a": 4,
        "b": 4,
        "result": 0
      }
    }
  ]
}